# Hello!

## I'm Shelby Courtney

I'm a Web Developer, trained in Front End Development and currently learning Python. I come from a rich Customer Service background with over 10 years in management roles for high volume and high traffic retail stores, and over 6 years in Interior Design. I believe software should be beautiful to look at, accessible to all, and easy to use from any experience level.



**CONTACT** ⋈ shelbycodes@gmail.com 281.630.9470 https://shelbycodes.me

## **Work Experience:**

#### 2016 - Present | Pottery Barn

Associate Store Manager - This role oversees sales and operations management, merchandising, and displays of a \$14M retail store.

#### 2019 - 2022 | Modsy

Remote Interior Designer - This role worked one-on-one with customers, creating a design vision and producing it into a 3D realization.

#### 2014 - 2016 | Anthropologie

Selling Department Manager - This role ran the sales team, hiring, and training for a \$9M retail store.

### **Education & Courses:**

#### **SheCodes**

**April 2022** 

Certified in Front End Development

May 2022

Certified in Responsive Web Development

June 2022

Certified in React Development

**BA** - Fashion Merchandising November 2014 International Academy of Design & Technology

**Technical Skills:** 







